#### **Brendan Mulhern**

Please Text - 603-828-5729
Or Please Email bmulhern@my365.bellevue.edu

Github: <a href="https://github.com/bmulhern2/">https://github.com/bmulhern2/</a>

<u>LinkedIn</u>: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/brendan-mulhern-1a72811ba/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/brendan-mulhern-1a72811ba/</a>

Website: https://brendan-mulhern.herokuapp.com

## Objective

My goal is to achieve an entry level position at a Company using Javascript. Preferably this position will be centered towards my studies: which recently have mostly been in Javascript. I have experience blogging for Medium about JavaScript mostly and you can find my Medium Articles here: <a href="https://earn-online.medium.com/">https://earn-online.medium.com/</a>. I also have experience blogging and doing video articles as well as podcasts. Please ask if you would like to view my Podcast or Video Articles. Also please check out my Github!

#### **About Me**

Hi my name is Brendan. I am an avid Javascript Developer centering my focus on Angular 10 and Server Side Development with Node.js. I am capable of creating robust APIs with HTTP and/or WebSockets and then I can get them with Angular (or React; or Vue; also with Vanilla HTML and Javascript). I have experience with working with JSON or Javascript Object Notation as my data format. MongoDB is the database I have most of my education in. I am capable of using MongoDB as a Real-Time database: meaning the client updates as the data is operated on. This includes GET requests; POST requests; PUT requests and DELETE requests. I am also capable of doing PATCH requests although it seems PATCH is the same as PUT though I might be wrong? Anyways I hope you enjoy reading my resume. Please text as I have blocked unknown callers on my iPhone as telemarketers have been calling a lot recently. Thank you and have a nice day.

## **University Projects**

Bob's Computer Repair Shop - 2020

- Worked in an Agile Team of Three Developers remotely.
- School Project For the Bellevue University Web Development Program
  - Project was built with a server and a client.
    - Many API's were used.
  - Angular's HTTP Client Module was used for frontend http.

#### NodeBucket - 2020

- Built "Trello" with the MEAN Stack.
  - This project was a solo effort.
- It was another project for the class MASTERING THE MEAN STACK BOOTCAMP.

- It's on my Github if you would like to take a look at it.

# **Other Experience**

Instacart - 2019 - 2021 - New England Area

- Worked as a Gig Worker and Grocery Shopper.

DoorDash - 2020 - 2021 - Dover, New Hampshire

- Another Gig I like to do
- It features delivering food to customers

UberEats - 2020 - 2021 - New Hampshire

- Pretty much the same as DoorDash

### **Education**

Bellevue University - 2019 -2021 - Web Development - Graduation - March 2021 - Remote

Oyster River High School - 2011 - Durham, New Hampshire